

Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science with 4.5 years of experience in Full Stack Development using HTML5, Angular 2/4/5/6, Ionic Framework 3/4, Bootstrap 4, Firebase, Typescript, Net Core(C#), Entity Framework Core, SQL Server, WebAPI.



Current Designation: Software Developer Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 6 Month(s)

Current Company: Financial Software Systems Notice Period: Currently Serving Notice Period

Current Location: Chennai Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Pref. Location: Chennai

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Software Development, Full stack development, C#.net, GIT, Android, .Net Core, SQL Server, Firebase, CSS, Java Script, Angular 2, Angular 4, Angular 6, Asp.Net core, Entity Framework, Typescript, Ionic, C#, WebApi, ASP.Net

MVC, LINQ, Html5

Verified: Email - id Phone Number |

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

Having around 4 years & 6 months of professional experience (June 2016 to Till Date) into the Full stack development using HTML5, IONIC FRAMEWORK,

ANGULAR 2/4/6/5, TYPESCRIPT, JAVASCRIPT, CSS3, Bootstrap 4, HighCharts, Chart. is, SQL SERVER, ASP.NET CORE(3.1), ENTITY FRAMEWORK CORE, GIT(GITHUB), LINQ

Work Experience

Financial Software Systems as Software Developer

Mar 2019 to Till Date

Working as a Full Stack Developer in Web, Android App development &IOS Development using Ionic Framework, Javascript Library, Typescript, Angular 4/5/6, HTML, Bootstrap 4 & Back End (Asp.Net core, C#, Entity Framework Core, SQL Server, WebAPI).

Changepond Technologies as Software Developer

Apr 2018 to Mar 2019

Worked as a Full Stack Developer in Web application and Android & IOS App development using Front End (Ionic Framework, Javascript Library, Typescript, Angular 4, Bootstrap 4) & Back End (Asp.Net core, C#, Entity Framework Core, SQL Server, WebAPI).

Learnteq Solutions as Programmer Trainee (Full stack)

Jun 2016 to Apr 2018

Learnteq Solutions, Bangalore (Software Developer (Full Stack) as - June 2016 to April 2018) ? 1 year and 10 months (2 years)

Worked with our Client - Learnteq Solutions from KARMYOG Karmyog Learning Solutions (Karmyog For 21st century) - (Jan 2016 to Dec 2017)

Continued as a employee of Learnteq Solutions from Jan 2018.

Working as a Full Stack Developer in Web application and Android App development using Ionic, Angular 2, bootstrapJavascript Library, Typescript and Firebase (Real Time Database), Asp.Net core, C#, Entity Framework, SQL Server, Web API, GIT

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from HINDUSTHAN INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, COIMBATORE in 2015

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience	
.Net Core(EF)	3.0	2020	4 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	
C#	6.0	2020	4 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	
Entity Framework Core	3	2020	4 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	
Angular	2/4/5/6	2020	4 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	
SQL Server		2020	4 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	
Visual Studio Code		2020	4 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	
HTML5	5	2020	4 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	
TypeScript	3.1	2020	4 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	
JavaScript		2020	4 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	
ionic framework	3/4	2020	4 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	
CSS	3	2020	4 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	
BOOTSTRAP		2020	4 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	
GIT		2020	4 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	
VISUAL STUDIO		2020	4 Year(s) 5 Month(s)	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			
Tamil	Expert			

Projects

Project Title: IOB Mobile Banking Client: Indian Overseas Bank Nature of Employment: Full Time Project Location: Chennai

Onsite / Offsite: Onsite Team Size: 2

Duration: Mar 2019 - Dec 2020

Role: Sr. Programmer Skill Used: Ionic framework, Angular 5, Angular 6, HTML, Typescript, JavaScript, .Net, ASP.Net, .Net Core, Asp.Net Core,

C#.Net, SQL Server, Entity Framework, WebApi

Project Details: Mobile Banking application for Fund transfer, NEFT, IMPS, Balance Enquiry, Deposits. Developed using Ionic

framework, Angular 5, 6 & Typescript and JavaScript, HTML 5

Project Title: Quest-Lite Client: Canaccord

Nature of Employment: Full Time **Duration: Apr 2018 - Mar 2019** Project Location: CHENNAI Onsite / Offsite: Onsite

Role: Sr. Programmer Team Size: 1

Skill Used: Ionic framework, Angular 5, Angular 6, HTML, Typescript, JavaScript, .Net, ASP.Net, .Net Core, Asp.Net Core,

C#.Net, SQL Server, Entity Framework, WebApi,

Project Details: Quest lite is about screening, Portfolios and current stock prices for various companies in various countries. Worked as a full stack developer in hybrid application android and ios using Ionic Framework, cordova, Angular 5, Typescript and .Net Core, C#, EF core, Sql Server(Back End).

Project Title: Ignite LMS Client: DCB Bank

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Jan 2017 - Mar 2018 Onsite / Offsite: Onsite Project Location: Bangalore

Role: Programmer Team Size: 6

Skill Used: Ionic Framework, Cordova, HTML 5, Angular 4, Type Script, C#.. Net core 2.0, Entity Framework, MSSQL Server

17.,

Project Details: It is based on Learning Management System. The users can take courses and attend tests through the

Android Application and Admin & trainers can Control all them through the web application

Project Title: TabMaster Client: Tata Trusts

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Jun 2016 - Jun 2017 Project Location: Bangalore Onsite / Offsite: Onsite Team Size: 3

Role: Programmer Skill Used: Ionic Framework, Angular 2, CSS, Firebase, Javascript library, Typescript,

Project Details: This project is collecting details of farmer in particular states and then collected land type, type of seed, facing

problems in their land.

Finally collect the report and submit the feedback to the trust (Ionic, Angular 2 and Firebase in VS code Environment).

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time